https://www.spiritfind.net/privacy.pl?Cat=Index&Dir=SpiritFind

Privacy Policy
Search:
in the entire directory
Angels and Nature SpiritsArtsAscensionChannelingChanneling/Channeled MaterialCommunicationCommunication/Chat RoomsCommunication/ForumsCommunication/Link ListsCommunication/Mailing ListsCommunication/NewslettersCommunication/Search EnginesCommunication/WebringsCommunity centers and churchesEducationEventsEvents/ConferencesEvents/ExhibitionsHealingHealing/Holistic PractitionersHealing/RemediesMeditationMiscellaneousMiscellaneous/Search EnginesMiscellaneous/Web DesignOraclesParanormal PhenomenaProducts and ServicesProducts and Services/BooksProducts and Services/Dream InterpretationProducts and Services/MusicProducts and Services/Psychic ReadingsProducts and Services/RetreatsProducts and Services/SeminarsProducts and Services/TravelProducts and Services/WorkshopsPropheciesSpiritual PathsSpiritual Paths/BuddhismSpiritual Paths/ChristianSpiritual Paths/CounselorsSpiritual Paths/Native AmericanSpiritual Paths/Online BooksSpiritual Paths/PaganSpiritual Paths/ScientologySpiritual Paths/StarseedSpiritual Paths/TantraSpiritual Paths/WiccaSpiritual Paths/YogaPrivacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase,or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To improve our website in order to better serve you.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To administer a contest or other site feature.
How do we protect your information?
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
We use an SSL certificate
All forms are redirected through https://sslsites.de to ensure an encrypted transmission of your data.
Do we use 'cookies'?
No.
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.
Third-party linksWe offer links to third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
On our Privacy Policy Page
You can change your personal information:
by logging in to your account
How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?No, we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify you via email
Within 1 business day
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
Send information such as notifications about the status of your application or entry, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
Allow users to unsubscribe by removing their listing.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can remove your listing
edit your listing to state DELETE as the title of your site listing
Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.Gerrit JahnCarrer Alt Camp 1DAltafulla, Catalonia 43893Spainadmin @ spiritfind . net
Visit our partner site MediumFind for a listing of mediums, psychics and readers!
This directory is not responsible for the content of external links.
